&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：当我们给变量赋值时，或者
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: When we assign some value to a variable, or
在第1行已经分配了任何内容的情况下，这种默认值，
in the case of line 1 having assigned anything, that sort of defaults,
然后我们使用typeof这样的运算符作为查看该值的第一种方法，并且
then we use an operator like typeof as our first way of looking at that value and
决定它的身份，它的种类，它的类型。
determining something about its identity, its kind, its type.
我们不是问变量v的类型，
And we're not asking what's the typeof the variable v,
我们问的是目前V中的值的类型是什么。
we're asking what is the typeof the value that is currently in v.
这就是第2行所说的。
That's what line 2 says.
当前v中的值的类型是什么？
What is the typeof the value that's currently in v?
您会注意到，在第2行，它返回字符串undefined。
And you'll notice that on line 2 it returns the string undefined.
现在这很有趣，因为本质上我们可以想到未定义的
Now that's interesting because essentially we can think of undefined
基本上作为默认值。
as basically a default value.
当空间的真空消除了所有其他东西时，它就存在了。
It's a value that exists when the vacuum of space has removed everything else.
当没有其他值时，
When there is no other value,
您拥有的值称为未定义的值。
the value that you have is called the undefined value.
记住，有一个未定义的类型
And remember, there's an undefined type with one and
其中只有一个值称为undefined。
only one value in it called undefined.
所以typeof告诉我们v当前是未定义的。
So typeof is telling us v currently is undefined.
它被初始化了，并且它是未定义的。
It got initialized and it's undefined.
顺便说一句，这并不意味着它还没有价值。
And that, by the way, does not mean it doesn't have a value yet.
很多人认为，未定义的意思还没有价值。
A lot of people think, undefined means doesn't have a value yet.
最合适的思考方式是，目前没有价值。
The most appropriate way to think about it is, does not currently have a value.
因为这是完全合理和可能的，而且经常发生，
Because it's entirely plausible and possible, and often happens,
您有一个变量或属性，该变量或属性具有一些值，并且
that you have a variable or a property that has some value and
然后它回到没有值的状态。
then it goes back to the state of not having a value anymore.
您将其设置为未定义，则取消定义它。
You set it to undefined, you undefine it.
这并不能消除它。
That doesn't remove it.
它不会删除它。
It doesn't delete it.
它不会神奇地让它消失。
It doesn't magically make it go away.
它只是将它带回它所持有的值未定义的状态。
It just takes it back to that state where the value that it's holding is undefined.
现在，当我赋值字符串并说typeof v时，我得到了引号字符串。
Now, when I assign the string and say typeof v, I get quote string.
当我分配一个号码时，我得到的是报价号码。
When I assign a number, I get quote number.
你会注意到
You'll notice that
typeof操作符的所有这些返回值都是字符串。
all of these return values from the typeof operator are strings.
这是至关重要的，我们稍后会看到为什么当我们进入强制，但是
That's critical and we'll see why later when we get into coercion, but
关键是你要明白这是一个运算符，可以保证
it's critical for you to understand this is an operator that guarantees
它总是返回一个字符串。
that it will always return a string.
它不仅总是返回字符串，
And not only will it always return a string,
它本质上是一个简短的eNom列表。
it's essentially a short eNom list.
只有一个非常小的字符串子集，它将永远返回。
There's only a very small subset of strings that it will ever return.
而且它们都不是空字符串。
And none of them are the empty string.
这些值都不是字符串，如null或undefined。
None of them are these values that aren't strings like null or undefined.
我在博客中经常看到这个错误。
And I see this mistake all the time in blogs.
人们会说平等的类型，平等的，没有定义的，
People will say typeof equal, equal undefined,
没有任何引号，这没有任何意义，因为
without any quotes and that makes no sense whatsoever because
typeof运算符实际上不能返回该值。
the typeof operator literally cannot return that.
猜猜我是怎么知道的。
Guess how I know.
我看了说明书。
I read the spec.
它不返回未定义的值，它总是返回字符串。
It does not return an undefined value, it always returns a string.
如果字符串是一个可预测的已知列表，那么我们已经减少了
And if the string is a predictable known list, then we've reduced
整个表面的混乱区域可能会从这里回来。
the whole surface area of confusion of what could possibly come back from this.
我们可以更好地预测其结果。
We can predict its outcome much better.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这在以后会很重要。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That'll be important later on.
所以typeof返回的字符串表示，嘿，
So typeof is returning strings that represent, hey,
这里有一些关于你可以期望能够做什么的线索
here's some clue as to what you can expect to be able to do with
这种特殊类型的值。
values of this particular kind of this particular type.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：从人体工程学的角度来看，这就是我们在代码中可以依赖的东西。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Ergonomically, that's what we can then rely upon in our code.
我们有一些东西将表现为一个数字。
We have something that is going to behave as a number.
我们有一些东西将表现为字符串。
We have something that is going to behave as a string.
你注意到我们并没有所有的值，就像我们没有一个typeof在里面一样
You notice we don't have all the values like we don't have a typeof within
一个数组给我们单词数组。
an array to give us the word array.
所以它只会把对象还给我们，因为记住，
So it's just gonna give us back object because remember,
阵列是对象的子类型。
arrays are subtypes of object.
所以我们需要进一步区分是否需要进入这些亚型，
So we're gonna need further distinguishing if we need to get into those subtypes,
但在最高级别，我们可以根据所有这些大致区分。
but at the top level we can distinguish roughly based on all of these.
现在，我提到了该列表上的NULL是特殊的。
Now, I mentioned the null being on that list as special.
你会注意到，当我们说typeof v等于null时，我很抱歉，
You'll notice that when we say typeof v equals null, I'm sorry,
当我们说v等于null和typeof v时，我们得到了引用对象。
when we say v equals null and typeof v, we get back quote object.
现在，这是JavaScript的历史事实。
Now, this is a historical fact of JavaScript.
事实上，在目前存在的规范中，
As a matter of fact, in the current spec that exists at this moment,
它仍然有一个来自ES1的语句，本质上
it still has a statement that was there from ES1 which essentially
向开发人员表明，如果要取消设置常规值，
indicated to developers that if you wanted to unset a regular value,
就像一个数字一样，你会使用undefined。
like a number, you would use undefined.
但如果要取消设置对象引用，则可以使用NULL。
But if you wanted to unset an object reference, you would use null.
我认为这是typeof null返回object的历史原因的一部分。
And I think that's part of the historical reason for why typeof null returns object.
但事情的真相是，我几年前在推特上说过，
But the real truth of the matter, I was tweeting about this years back,
而事实的真相是，这只是一个虫子。
and the real truth of the matter is that it's just a bug.
它应该返回引用NULL来告诉我们这是一个值
It ought to have returned quote null to tell us that this a value of
类型为NULL。
the type null.
不幸的是，它返回Quote对象，所以您必须更加小心。
Unfortunately, it returns quote object, so you have to be a little bit more careful.
你必须确保，当你做类型检查和
You have to make sure, when you're doing a typeof check and
它返回Object，确保它不是意外的NULL，
it returns object, make sure that it's not accidentally the null,
因为这样你就不会得到一个对象，而是一个空值。
because then you're not gonna get an object but a null value.
然后我们在这里看到函数。
And then we see function here.
请记住，函数不是正式类型
Remember, function is not an official type
在最高级别，在最官方的意义上。
at the top level, in the most official sense.
但在这里它有自己的返回值，typeof操作符作为函数返回。
But it has its own return value here, the typeof operator returns as function.
所以它返回给我们函数是有用的，但是数组，它不是。
So it's useful that it returns to us function, but arrays, it doesn't.
数组只返回对象。
Arrays just returns object.
其中很多只是，再次，关于JavaScript的历史事件。
A lot of these are just, again, historical things about JavaScript.
我们不能修复它们，因为如果我们修复它们，我们就会破坏一堆代码。
We can't fix them because if we fix them, we'd break a bunch of code.
所以与其抱怨或抱怨，
So rather than whine or complain about them,
我们应该学习它们，然后绕过它们，好吗？
we should just learn them and work around them, okay?
很遗憾你不能只说typeof，但是
It's regrettable that you can't just say typeof, but
语言中还有其他助手，特别是关于数组，
there are other helpers in language, in particular, with respect to array,
有一个Array.isArray，它会肯定地告诉您是否有一个数组。
there's Array.isArray, and it'll tell you for sure or not whether you have an array.
这就是我们如何区分这些原始值和它们的类型。
So that's how we distinguish these primitive values with their types.
我们可以使用像typeof这样的实用程序，当我们需要更多细节时，
We can use utilities like typeof and when we need a little bit more specifics,
更多的细微差别，我们可以使用像Array.isArray这样的实用程序。
a little bit more nuance, we can use utilities like Array.isArray.
他们会告诉我们一些关于价值本质的东西，告诉我们什么
They'll tell us something about the nature of the value which tells us what
我们可以期待。
we can expect.